Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
In this video, let's look at a few more utility methods which are present in the String class as well as
在这个视频中，让我们再看看字符串类中的一些实用方法，以及
we would discuss something very important called concatenation operator.
我们将讨论一个非常重要的东西，叫做连接运算符。
Let's start with the concatenation operator which is +, right. So, we looked at 1 + 2, what would be
让我们从连接运算符开始，它是+，对。那么，我们看一下1+2，会是什么
the value? It would return 3. The same thing if I do strings,
值是多少？它将返回3。同样的事情，如果我做字符串。
what would be the output? Think about it.
输出会是什么？想一想吧。
It's 12.
它是12。
So, it actually just concatenates 1 with 2 and returns it back. Let's say one of these is a string
所以，它实际上只是把1和2连接起来，然后返回。比方说，其中一个是字符串
and the other one is number.
而另一个是数字。
Will the value change? Nope.
这个值会改变吗？不会。
It is "1" + 2.
它是 "1"+2。
So, if the number is 23, let's say, it's 123.
所以，如果数字是23，比方说，它是123。
However, just 1 + 23 would return 24.
然而，只是1+23会返回24。
So, if there is a string in one of the operands, then what would happen? Is it becomes concatenation,
那么，如果其中一个操作数有一个字符串，那么会发生什么？它变成了连接。
+ behaves as if this is a concatenation. So, 1 is concatenated to 23.
+的行为就像这是一个串联。所以，1被串联到23。
So, 123. However, there are no strings. 1 + 23 is returning back,
所以，123。然而，没有任何字符串。1+23是返回的。
24. If I have 1 + 2+ "3", what would be the result? Right,
24. 如果我有1+2+"3"，结果会是什么？对。
it's printing 33.
它打印的是33。
Let's try a different thing.
让我们尝试一下不同的事情。
Let's say I don't do this, but I would do this. 123,
假设我不这样做，但我会这样做。123,
that's interesting,
这很有趣。
right.
对。
So, why is this happening? The way expressions are evaluated in Java are left to right. So, left starts with
那么，为什么会出现这种情况呢？Java中表达式的评估方式是从左到右。所以，左边开始是
1.
So, 1 + 2 is 3.
所以，1+2就是3。
So, this is performed as an integer operation. So, any normal, any operation between two integers is a integer.
所以，这是作为一个整数操作来执行的。所以，任何正常的，两个整数之间的操作都是一个整数。
So, 1 + 2 will return 3.
所以，1+2将返回3。
However, once there is 3, the result of this is 3, once we have the result,
然而，一旦有了3，这个结果就是3，一旦我们有了结果。
now, it's 3 + string 3, then it becomes concatenation. So, that's why it is 33.
现在，它是3+字符串3，那么它就变成了连接。所以，这就是为什么它是33。
In this case, let's start from the left, 1 + 2 is 1, is a string, 2 is an integer.
在这种情况下，让我们从左边开始，1+2是1，是一个字符串，2是一个整数。
So, the result is a string.
所以，结果是一个字符串。
So, 1 + 2  becomes concatenation, 12 and 12 is a string again. To that, we are appending 3.
所以，1+2成为连接，12，12又是一个字符串。在此基础上，我们再加上3。
So, 123.
所以，123。
So, the rules of concatenation are very simple. It executes from left to right
所以，连接的规则非常简单。它从左到右执行
and if you see two integers as part of the operation, it would be addition. If you see one string and
而如果你看到两个整数作为操作的一部分，这将是加法。如果你看到一个字符串和
one integer, it's concatenation.
一个整数，这就是连接。
If it's both strings, then it's concatenation as well.
如果是两个字符串，那也是连接。
Okay.
好的。
That's how we would do a lot of our printing, right. So, whenever we did System.out.println,
这就是我们如何进行大量的打印，对吧。所以，每当我们做System.out.println,
we were using +,
我们都是用+。
right.
对。
So, if I have a integer variable, let's say int
所以，如果我有一个整数变量，比方说int
i = 20.
I can do System.out.println
我可以做System.out.println
"Value is" and we said + 20,
"值是"，我们说+20。
right.
对。
So, this is how we did it.
所以，我们就是这样做的。
"Value is 20" is printed.
"值为20 "被打印出来。
This is because of the concatenation operator: string and int. String and int, it becomes concatenation.
这是因为串联运算符：字符串和int。字符串和int，它变成了连接。
So, if I'm doing + 20, what would be the result?
所以，如果我在做+20，结果会是什么？
Value is 2020;
值是2020。
it's just concatenation. Try a puzzle, right. So,
这只是串联。试着做一道题，对。所以。
if you want now, I would want to print 40.
如果你现在想，我想打印40。
What can I do?
我可以做什么呢？
What can I do is, put it in brackets.
我可以做的是，把它放在括号里。
Once you'd put it something in brackets, the brackets get priority.
一旦你把它放在括号里的东西，括号就会得到优先权。
So,
所以。
Value is 40.
值是40。
Let's look at a few other utility methods which are present in the String class.
让我们来看看字符串类中的其他一些实用方法。
So, this is a static method which is present in String.
所以，这是一个存在于String中的静态方法。
This is join method. Lot of scenarios, you would want to append comma to a list of numbers, right. So,
这就是连接方法。在很多情况下，你想在一个数字列表中添加逗号，对吗？所以。
if I want a string with 2, 3, 4, so I can do something of this kind.
如果我想要一个有2、3、4的字符串，那么我可以做这样的事情。
This returns, the first character is what character you want to join with, and rest is a list of strings
这个返回，第一个字符是你想加入的字符，其余的是你想加入的字符串的列表
that you would want to append.
你想追加的字符串列表。
So, 2, 3, 4.
所以，2、3、4。
So, if I just have lesser number values, let's say 35 or 'A', let's say this is 'B', and this is 'C'. It prints A, B, C
所以，如果我只是有较少的数字值，比方说35或'A'，比方说这是'B'，这是'C'。它打印出A、B、C
and if there is only one, it just prints 'A'. If there are two, it would start appending a ','. So, this is a
如果只有一个，它只打印'A'。如果有两个，它就会开始附加一个'，'。所以，这是一个
very useful utility thing when you would want to separate the different values inside a string using
当你想用','来分隔一个字符串中的不同值时，这是一个非常有用的工具。
a ','.
The last utility method is to replace.
最后一个实用方法是替换。
So, let's say, in this string, I would want to replace a specific character. So, I can say replace character "a"
所以，假设在这个字符串中，我想替换一个特定的字符。所以，我可以说替换字符 "a"
with character "z". What would be the output? "zbcd" or you can say, even replace a string, right. So, replace
与字符 "z"。输出会是什么？"zbcd "或者你可以说，甚至替换一个字符串，对吧。所以，把
"ab" with "xyz". So, it becomes "xyzcd".
"ab "与 "xyz"。所以，它就变成了 "xyzcd"。
That's cool right.
这很好，对。
So, what we are doing is, it's trying to explore the string APIs. One of the important things is trying to
所以，我们正在做的是，它正试图探索字符串API。其中一件重要的事情是试图
discover and understand the APIs might become little boring after a while.
发现和理解这些API可能会在一段时间后变得有点无聊。
There are so many different methods that are present, that it's impossible to remember all of them.
有这么多不同的方法存在，要记住所有的方法是不可能的。
I think the way you can look at it is, try to understand what are the possibilities that are there.
我认为你可以这样看待它，试着去理解有哪些可能性。
What are the possible operations that are present?
有哪些可能的操作是存在的？
You don't really need to remember all the method names that are present.
你真的不需要记住所有存在的方法名称。
If you are unable to find out what is the right method to do something, you can just say,
如果你无法找出正确的方法来做某事，你可以直接说。
let's say, I have a string variable, right str = 25 or some text, right.
比方说，我有一个字符串变量，str = 25或一些文本，对吧。
I can just say str. and it would show you all the different operations which are present on that
我可以直接说str.然后它就会向你显示对该字符串的所有不同操作。
specific string. So, you can try and research that method further and see if that matches your needs
特定的字符串。所以，你可以尝试进一步研究这个方法，看看是否符合你的需要。
and also there would be a few static methods which are present. So, you can type the class name and press
也会有一些静态方法存在。所以，你可以输入类的名称，然后按
'.' and press tab and that would print all the static methods that are present in there.
'.'，然后按tab键，这样就可以打印出其中所有的静态方法。
We have not really discussed every method which is present in there because that means we'll be spending
我们没有真正讨论其中的每一个方法，因为这意味着我们将花费整个课程来讨论字符串。
the entire course just discussing the string API.
整个课程都在讨论字符串API。
But the idea was to capture the essentials and give them to you and at any other point if you would
但我们的想法是抓住要点，把它们交给你，在任何其他时候，如果你想了解
want to find out whether such kind of feature is there, you can just type in str. or string.
想知道是否有这样的功能，你可以直接输入str.或string.
and find out what are the other options which are present. The other way you can do to explore the API
并找出存在的其他选项。你可以用另一种方法来探索API
is to type in Java doc and type in the class you would want to explore and say which version. Since I would
是键入Java doc，然后键入你想探索的类，并说明是哪个版本。因为我想
want to look at the string class in Java 9,
想看看Java 9中的字符串类。
I'd want to look at the Java doc for it.
我想看看它的Java文档。
You can take this and this would show the entire documentation for the String class.
你可以拿着这个，这将显示整个字符串类的文档。
So, as you can see in here, it says, the String class represents character strings. All string literals in
所以，正如你在这里看到的，它说，字符串类代表字符串。Java程序中的所有字符串字面
Java programs such as "abc" are implemented as instances of this class
中的所有字符串字面，例如 "abc"，都是作为这个类的实例实现的。
and if you look at it, it says Strings are constants, their values cannot be changed after they're created,
如果你看一下，它说字符串是常量，它们的值在创建后不能被改变。
right.
对。
We'll talk about StringBuffers later. But the idea is,  you can actually look at the documentation in
我们稍后会谈论StringBuffers。但是我们的想法是，你实际上可以看一下这里的文档
here.
这里。
Let's say you would want to explore a specific method,
比方说，你想探索一个特定的方法。
what it does, concat what it does,
它做什么，它做什么。
you can just click the method and look at examples down there as well.
你可以直接点击该方法，然后看看下面的例子。
So, one of the things I would recommend you to do is, try and look at the APIs and try and understand the
所以，我建议你做的一件事是，尝试看看API，并尝试了解
different methods which are present.
不同的方法。
It's impossible to remember all the APIs.
要记住所有的API是不可能的。
So, try and get an awareness of what can be done and whenever the need arises,
所以，试着去了解可以做什么，并且在需要的时候。
you go and search the documentation to find the right methods. Until the next video, bye-bye.
你就去搜索文档，找到正确的方法。在下一个视频之前，拜拜。